If it's background noise, please ignore it a little,
guys.  So, after a long time, I
found some time this evening.  The reason is that the
computer applications teacher
did not teach this evening.  So I think I started my
studies very poorly.
Since my studies started in mid-year
and I wasn't using any new stationery
or appliances.
So today I went to our
stationery shop here and
bought two notebooks, both new and old. I
recycled them and differentiated the subject-wise
notebooks. I
made separate notebooks for the school and
put labels on the books so that
everything is manageable in a limited and clean way. I
cleaned the bag and
cleaned the stationery pouch.  And the big house is a mess
and I
need to clean it up.  And
I'm very sorry for the videos coming so late.
Because I'm in a lot of trouble right now.  I ca
n't manage anything.  But giving you the video is
my own choice.  So I will definitely keep
making videos and art-related videos will definitely
come.  So don't worry guys.
And if you want a long video
related to study or according to the study blog or
according to my study life, you
can comment on it and I will
make a video for you on YouTube and
you will get the link to that video on Instagram.